<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UHealth</string>

    <string name="policy">
Privacy Policy for U Health \n
Privacy Policy \n
Last updated: April 10, 2021 \n

This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You. \n\n

We use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy has been created with the help of the Privacy Policy Generator. \n\n

Interpretation and Definitions \n
Interpretation \n
The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions. The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural. \n\n

Definitions \n
For the purposes of this Privacy Policy: \n\n

Account means a unique account created for You to access our Service or parts of our Service. \n\n

Affiliate means an entity that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with a party, where "control" means ownership of 50% or more of the shares, equity interest or other securities entitled to vote for election of directors or other managing authority. \n\n

Application means the software program provided by the Company downloaded by You on any electronic device, named U Health \n\n

Company (referred to as either "the Company", "We", "Us" or "Our" in this Agreement) refers to U Health. \n\n

Country refers to: Ontario, Canada \n\n

Device means any device that can access the Service such as a computer, a cellphone or a digital tablet. \n\n

Personal Data is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable individual. \n\n

Service refers to the Application. \n\n

Service Provider means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Company. It refers to third-party companies or individuals employed by the Company to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on behalf of the Company, to perform services related to the Service or to assist the Company in analyzing how the Service is used. \n\n

Third-party Social Media Service refers to any website or any social network website through which a User can log in or create an account to use the Service. \n\n

Usage Data refers to data collected automatically, either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit). \n\n

You means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable. \n\n

Collecting and Using Your Personal Data \n
Types of Data Collected \n
Personal Data \n
While using Our Service, We may ask You to provide Us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify You. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to: \n\n

Email address \n\n

First name and last name \n\n

Phone number \n\n

Usage Data \n\n

Usage Data \n
Usage Data is collected automatically when using the Service. \n\n

Usage Data may include information such as Your Device\'s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that You visit, the time and date of Your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data. \n\n

When You access the Service by or through a mobile device, We may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device You use, Your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of Your mobile device, Your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser You use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data. \n\n

We may also collect information that Your browser sends whenever You visit our Service or when You access the Service by or through a mobile device. \n\n

Use of Your Personal Data \n
The Company may use Personal Data for the following purposes: \n\n

To provide and maintain our Service, including to monitor the usage of our Service. \n\n

To manage Your Account: to manage Your registration as a user of the Service. The Personal Data You provide can give You access to different functionalities of the Service that are available to You as a registered user. \n\n

For the performance of a contract: the development, compliance and undertaking of the purchase contract for the products, items or services You have purchased or of any other contract with Us through the Service. \n\n

To contact You: To contact You by email, telephone calls, SMS, or other equivalent forms of electronic communication, such as a mobile application\'s push notifications regarding updates or informative communications related to the functionalities, products or contracted services, including the security updates, when necessary or reasonable for their implementation. \n\n

To provide You with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless You have opted not to receive such information. \n\n

To manage Your requests: To attend and manage Your requests to Us. \n\n

For business transfers: We may use Your information to evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which Personal Data held by Us about our Service users is among the assets transferred. \n\n

For other purposes: We may use Your information for other purposes, such as data analysis, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and to evaluate and improve our Service, products, services, marketing and your experience. \n\n

We may share Your personal information in the following situations: \n\n

With Service Providers: We may share Your personal information with Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service, to contact You. \n
For business transfers: We may share or transfer Your personal information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of Company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of Our business to another company. \n
With Affiliates: We may share Your information with Our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. Affiliates include Our parent company and any other subsidiaries, joint venture partners or other companies that We control or that are under common control with Us. \n
With business partners: We may share Your information with Our business partners to offer You certain products, services or promotions. \n
With other users: when You share personal information or otherwise interact in the public areas with other users, such information may be viewed by all users and may be publicly distributed outside. If You interact with other users or register through a Third-Party Social Media Service, Your contacts on the Third-Party Social Media Service may see Your name, profile, pictures and description of Your activity. Similarly, other users will be able to view descriptions of Your activity, communicate with You and view Your profile. \n
With Your consent: We may disclose Your personal information for any other purpose with Your consent. \n
Retention of Your Personal Data \n
The Company will retain Your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use Your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies. \n\n

The Company will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of Our Service, or We are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods. \n\n

Transfer of Your Personal Data \n
Your information, including Personal Data, is processed at the Company\'s operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located. It means that this information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of Your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from Your jurisdiction. \n\n

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by Your submission of such information represents Your agreement to that transfer. \n\n

The Company will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that Your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of Your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of Your data and other personal information. \n\n

Disclosure of Your Personal Data \n
Business Transactions \n
If the Company is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, Your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before Your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy. \n\n

Law enforcement \n
Under certain circumstances, the Company may be required to disclose Your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency). \n\n

Other legal requirements \n
The Company may disclose Your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: \n\n

Comply with a legal obligation \n
Protect and defend the rights or property of the Company \n
Prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service \n
Protect the personal safety of Users of the Service or the public \n
Protect against legal liability \n
Security of Your Personal Data \n
The security of Your Personal Data is important to Us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect Your Personal Data, We cannot guarantee its absolute security. \n\n

Changes to this Privacy Policy \n
We may update Our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify You of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. \n\n

Contact Us \n
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, You can contact us: \n\n

By phone number: 123456789 \n
Privacy Policy for U Health
    </string>

    <string-array name="Preventative_Health">
        <item>Cardiovascular diseases are the number one cause of death among patients with prostate cancer, take care of your heart!</item>
        <item>Obesity, smoking, and a sedentary life are things that we should prevent to take care of our overall health</item>
        <item>If you are 50 years old or older, remember to do screening of colorectal cancer, ask your Family Physician about the recommendations</item>
        <item>Prostate cancer is present in 1 out of 7 men, you are not alone</item>
        <item>Feeling anxious about your prostate cancer diagnosis? Ask your doctor about advocacy groups available in your area, you are not alone!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="gender_option">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Appointment_types">
        <item>office appointment</item>
        <item>chemotherapy</item>
        <item>surgery or procedure appointment</item>
        <item>radiation session</item>
        <item>imaging appointment</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Diag_Category">
        <item>Neurological Diseases</item>
        <item>Sensory Diseases</item>
        <item>Endocrine Diseases</item>
        <item>Cardiovascular Diseases</item>
        <item>Lung Diseases</item>
        <item>Gastrointestinal Diseases</item>
        <item>Genitourinary Disorders</item>
        <item>Vascular Diseases</item>
        <item>Rheumatoid Diseases</item>
        <item>Cancers</item>
        <item>Miscellaneous</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Neurological_Disease">
        <item>History of stroke</item>
        <item>Multiple sclerosis</item>
        <item>Brain Tumor</item>
        <item>History of seizures</item>
        <item>Epilepsy</item>
        <item>Cerebral palsy</item>
        <item>Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis</item>
        <item>Autism Spectrum disorder</item>
        <item>Attention deficit and hyperactivity disorder</item>
        <item>Head or neck injuries</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Sensory_Disease">
        <item>Blindness or near-blindness</item>
        <item>Deafness or near-deafness</item>
        <item>Loss of taste</item>
        <item>Loss of sense of smell</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Endocrine_Disease">
        <item>Diabetes mellitus</item>
        <item>Diabetes insipidus</item>
        <item>Hypothyroidism</item>
        <item>Hyperthyroidism</item>
        <item>Parathyroid abnormalities</item>
        <item>Hypogonadism</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Cardiovascular_Disease">
        <item>History of myocardial infraction</item>
        <item>Angina</item>
        <item>Systemic arterial hypertension</item>
        <item>Heart failure</item>
        <item>Heart valve disease</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Lung_Disease">
        <item>History of smoking</item>
        <item>Idiopatic pulmonary fibrosis</item>
        <item>Emphysema</item>
        <item>Asthma</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Gastrointestinal_Disease">
        <item>Gastroesophageal reflux</item>
        <item>Swallowing disorder</item>
        <item>Gastritis</item>
        <item>History of pancreatitis</item>
        <item>Constipation</item>
        <item>Chronic diarrhea</item>
        <item>Short bowel syndrome</item>
        <item>Diverticular disease</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Genitourinary_Disorders">
        <item>Kidney stones</item>
        <item>Kidney cysts</item>
        <item>Benign kidney tumors</item>
        <item>Single kidney</item>
        <item>Hypoactive bladder</item>
        <item>Hyperactive bladder</item>
        <item>Benign prostatic growth</item>
        <item>History of sexually transmitted disease</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Vascular_Disease">
        <item>History of aneurism</item>
        <item>Vasculitis</item>
        <item>Venous insufficiency</item>
        <item>Venous thromboembolism</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Rheumatoid_Disease">
        <item>Lupus</item>
        <item>Rheumatoid arthritis</item>
        <item>Fybromialgia</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Cancer"></string-array>

    <string-array name="Miscellaneous">
        <item>Human immunodeficiency syndrome</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="default_str">a</string>
    <string name="title_activity_appointmnet_list">AppointmnetList</string>
    <string name="title_activity_medication_list">MedicationList</string>
    <string name="title_activity_appointment_adder">AppointmentAdder</string>
    <string name="title_activity_medication_adder">MedicationAdder</string>
    <string name="medicine_name">add medicine name</string>
    <string name="appointment_location">add appointment location</string>
    <string name="select_date">Select date</string>
    <string name="select_time">Select time</string>
    <string name="physcian_name">add physcian name</string>
    <string name="add_appointment">Add an appointment!</string>
    <string name="interval">frequency of the medication(measured by hours)</string>
    <string name="storage">available storage for your first repeat</string>
    <string name="add_medication">Add a medication plan</string>

    <string name="select_appointment_type">Select appointment type</string>
    <string name="office_appointment">office appointment</string>
    <string name="start_of_medication">Start of Medication</string>
    <string name="repeats_count">enter the number of repeats</string>
    <string name="dosis">dosis per time(measured by the storage unit)</string>


    <string name="title_activity_appointment_updater">AppointmentUpdater</string>

    <string name="notes"><b>Notes:</b></string>
    <string name="meds"><b>Medications</b></string>
    <string name="additional"><b>Additional Files</b></string>
    <string name="fsv_explain_title"><b>Requesting Information</b></string>
    <string name="fsv_explain_content">You may request a snapshot of personal information from another user, permission must be granted from the requested and they will choose which information they would like to share with you.
        Including: \n\n
        \u2022 Personal Information and Medical History \n
        \u2022 Diagnosis Histroy \n
        \u2022 Timeline \n
    </string>
    <string name="fsv_request_title"><b>Enter requested user\'s E-mail</b></string>
    <string name="DF_outstanding_accept_explain">I agree to share the following information:</string>

    <string name="ECOG_Description">To conduct clinical trials for the treatment of cancer in a consistent manner across many participating hospitals, cancer centers, and clinics requires the use of standard criteria for measuring how the disease impacts a patient’s daily living abilities (known to physicians and researchers as a patient’s performance status). The ECOG Scale of Performance Status is one such measurement. It describes a patient’s level of functioning in terms of their ability to care for themself, daily activity, and physical ability (walking, working, etc.).
    \n\n
    Researchers worldwide take the ECOG Performance Status into consideration when planning trials to study a new treatment method. This numbering scale is one way to define the population of patients to be studied in the trial, so that it can be uniformly reproduced among physicians who enroll patients. It is also a way for physicians to track changes in a patient’s level of functioning as a result of treatment during the trial.</string>
    <string name="ECOG_Interpretation">\n
    0 - Fully active, able to carry on all pre-disease performance without restriction \n\n
    1 - Restricted in physically strenuous activity but ambulatory and able to carry out work of a light or sedentary nature, e.g., light house work, office work\n\n
    2 - Ambulatory and capable of all selfcare but unable to carry out any work activities; up and about more than 50% of waking hours \n\n
        3 - Capable of only limited selfcare; confined to bed or chair more than 50% of waking hours \n\n
        4 - Completely disabled; cannot carry on any selfcare; totally confined to bed or chair \n\n
        5 - Dead
    </string>
    <string name="ECOG_Furthermore">https://ecog-acrin.org/resources/ecog-performance-status</string>

    <string name="ICIQ_Description">The ICIQ-UI Short Form is a questionnaire for evaluating the frequency, severity and impact on quality of life (QoL) of urinary incontinence in men and women in research and clinical practice across the world. This short and simple questionnaire is also of use to general practitioners and clinicians in both primary and secondary care institutions to screen for incontinence, to obtain a brief yet comprehensive summary of the level, impact and perceived cause of symptoms of incontinence and to facilitate patient-clinician discussions.</string>
    <string name="ICIQ_Interpretation">
        \u2022 The ICIQ is a self-reported survey and screening tool for incontinence \n\n
        \u2022 Scoring scale: 0-21, minimum 0, maximum 21. A higher score indicates greater impairment from incontinence. \n\n
        \u2022 Item-level scores vary but range from 0-10. Item (question) 6 (self-perceived cause) is unscored \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="ICIQ_Furthermore">https://www.sralab.org/rehabilitation-measures/international-consultation-incontinence-questionnaire-short-form</string>

    <string name="IIEF_Description">These questions ask about the effects that your erection problems have had on your sex life over the
last four weeks. Please try to answer the questions as honestly and as clearly as you are able. Your
answers will help your doctor to choose the most effective treatment suited to your condition. In
        answering the questions, the following definitions apply:
        \n\n
        - <b>Sexual activity</b> includes intercourse, caressing, foreplay &amp; masturbation \n\n
        - <b>Sexual intercourse</b> is defined as sexual penetration of your partner \n\n
        - <b>Sexual stimulation</b> includes situation such as foreplay, erotic pictures etc. \n\n
        - <b>Ejaculation</b> is the ejection of semen from the penis (or the feeling of this) \n\n
        - <b>Orgasm</b> is the fulfilment or climax following sexual stimulation or intercourse \n\n
</string>
    <string name="IIEF_Interpretation">
        \u2022 1-10: Severe Erectile Dysfunction \n\n
        \u2022 11-16: Moderate dysfunction \n\n
        \u2022 17-21: Mild to moderate dysfunction \n\n
        \u2022 22-25: Mild dysfunction \n\n
        \u2022 26+: No dysfunction \n\n
       </string>
    <string name="IIEF_Furthermore">https://www.baus.org.uk/_userfiles/pages/files/Patients/Leaflets/iief.pdf</string>
    <string name="further_information"><u>Further Information</u></string>
    <string name="event"><b>Event:</b></string>
    <string name="location"><b>date:</b></string>
    <string name="listofappointments">List of Appointments</string>

</resources>